Hey — I'm Don Jordan, founder of CTV Homes,
and a real estate broker in the Poconos.
Before I lose you with a buzzword: CTV
stands for Connected TV.
But forget the term. All it really means
is watching TV through streaming apps.
Netflix, Hulu, Peacock, Pluto, Roku, Fire
Stick, Apple TV.
Any app on a smart TV. That's it — you
already do it every night.
Here's why that matters. Because those
apps run on the internet, advertisers can
pick exactly which households see an ad —
right down to the ZIP code.
And over the last sixty days, I ran
forty-five thousand of those TV ads across
my own listings, for under four cents
each.
Real TV. Real networks. Pennies. Let me
show you how.
Here's the one sentence that makes this
whole thing click.
Connected TV is the new postcard. You
already know the postcard play.
You mail a Just Listed or a Just Sold card
to your farm.
Not to get a call that afternoon — but to
stay top of mind, so when someone on
that street decides to sell, your name is
the one they already know.
That's farming. It works. The problem
isn't the strategy — it's the postcard.
It's expensive, most of it gets thrown
out, and you can't tell if anyone ever
saw it. Connected TV is that same farming
strategy — your name, your face, your
listings, in front of your farm, over and
over — except it's cheaper, it's on
the biggest screen in their house, and we
can actually prove it ran.
Let's be honest about the postcard. The
average homeowner gets forty-one pieces
of mail a week, and about eighty-two
percent goes straight into the recycling.
The real call rate on real estate direct
mail is around four hundredths of one
percent. That's four calls for every ten
thousand cards.
And ten thousand cards cost you six, maybe
seven thousand dollars.
The other options aren't any better. Zillow
Premier got more expensive in twenty
twenty-six — a hundred and thirty-nine to
two hundred and twenty-three dollars
per connection, plus three hundred to two
thousand dollars a month just to be
in the queue. And that same lead gets sold
to three or four other agents.
Go the Flex route instead, and you hand
over thirty-five to forty percent of your
commission. Organic social media? Business
page reach is under three percent.
You post, it's buried by lunch, and almost
none of your followers ever see it.
You're not short on effort. You're short
on a channel that actually gets seen
— at a price that makes sense.
So here's the upgrade. A postcard costs
you fifty cents to a dollar twenty each
— and gets tossed. A Connected TV impression
costs about four cents — and it lands
on a sixty-five inch screen during the
evening news.
Same farm. Same goal — stay top of mind.
But instead of paper in a junk-mail pile,
you're on Hulu, on Roku, on Peacock
— in only the households you picked. Your
face.
Your name. Your number. For pennies. That's
not a different strategy than farming.
It's the same strategy your business is
already built on — just on the screen
people actually pay attention to.
Now I want to be straight with you,
because this matters.
This is not a phone rings off the hook
tomorrow tool.
Neither is a postcard. Neither is a
billboard.
This is an awareness play. It's about
frequency.
The first time someone sees you — who's
that?
Nothing happens. The third time — I've
seen them somewhere.
The seventh time — that's the agent on TV.
The twelfth time — my neighbor used them,
let's call.
Most agents quit at impression three. They
run one campaign, see no calls, panic,
and shut it off. The ones who don't quit
become the famous agent in their farm.
Connected TV is just the cheapest way
ever invented to hit those twelve-plus impressions
on the right households.
Here's the part that makes this better
than any postcard or billboard ever could
be. When your TV ad plays in a household,
we don't stop there.
The platform also runs clickable banner
ads to those same homes — on their phone,
their tablet, their laptop. We call it
multi-touch.
They see you on the big screen at night,
then your banner shows up while they're
scrolling the next day — and that one,
they can tap.
So the TV builds the recognition, and the
banners give them a way to act on it.
A billboard can't do that. A postcard
can't do that.
I'm not pitching theory. These are my
numbers, my money, my listings.
One of my listings. Seventeen days.
Twenty-four thousand impressions.
Eighty-eight hundred unique households.
Average frequency, two point seven —
that's dead in the recognition zone.
People saw me about three times, not once.
The cost came in at a thirty-six dollar
CPM, for premium, hyper-local streaming.
Three to five times cheaper than old
broadcast TV.
Run that across listings over sixty days,
and that's the forty-five thousand impressions
for under four cents each I mentioned up
top.
Same broker, same market, same playbook
I'm about to hand you.
And here's the kicker — you don't need an
agency, a film crew, or a five thousand
dollar production budget. You make the whole
ad yourself, in about ninety seconds.
Watch. I paste in a Zillow link. I click
one button.
And the AI writes the script, picks the
shots, records the voiceover, and builds
a broadcast-quality, thirty-second TV ad —
start to finish — in about a minute
and a half. That's the whole skill curve.
( A finished CTV Homes ad — for a real
listing )
Built from a Zillow link in 90 seconds.
So here's what I want you to do. Don't
take my word for it — go make one.
Your first ad is free. Paste in one of
your listings and watch it build the exact
ad I just showed you. No crew, no
contract, no risk.
Go to ctvhomes dot com, build your first
ad on us, and see your own listing on
real TV. You'll be the only agent in your
ZIP who's figured this out — for now.
I'm Don Jordan. Thanks for watching. Now
go make your first one.